The Western envoy is dead
The Truth-telling Gu is gone
The Dragon Jade remains missing to this day
Do you all have a death wish?
My dear Chen, I didn't mean to
What about Li Zhi'an then?
Where is Li Zhi'an?
Chen... my dear Chen
Li Zhi'an
Your Highness the Third Prince, what are you doing?
Damn you!
Speak!
Where is the Dragon Jade?
You're drunk
What's wrong?
Guards! Escort the Third Prince back to rest immediately
Still won't reveal the Dragon Jade's whereabouts?
Are you trying to ruin all my efforts?
Your Highness mustn't do this!
I'm not some weakling to be trampled upon
You keep professing your love for me
Now you'd raise your hand against me over the Dragon Jade
If my lord has no affection left for me
You may simply divorce me
If you think you can take advantage of my blindness
I'm quite skilled at locating by sound
Today we fight to the death
Or I, Li Zhi'an, am unworthy of my military lineage
You damned blind woman! How dare you strike me!
Zhu Huaijin!
Have you fallen for her?
Your Highness is drunk
If this matter reaches His Majesty and the ministers
It would be most inappropriate
Guards!
Escort His Highness back
My dear Chen
Thank you for your assistance, Seventh Brother
I won't let this matter rest
Please summon my Li family to discuss the divorce
Are you alright?
This cold compress medicine works wonders
I'll have someone bring it to you later
It's alright, Hua Mei
Help me back
Yes
How dare you touch my woman
Zhu Huaichen
You must have a death wish
Assassin!
Catch the assassin!
Assassin! Get the assassin!
Chen Lang
Search separately
We must catch that assassin
Understood
That assassin's movements just now...
That was clearly Zhu Huaijin
He went to assassinate Zhu Huaichen
Your Highness, last night the Third Prince...
Zhu Huaichen is dead
No, that's not...
Last night an assassin cut off the Third Prince's hand
Is he standing up for me?
Useless
A bunch of good-for-nothings
We must find that assassin
And make him suffer a thousand cuts
Dear Chen, don't be angry
I've found the most skilled craftsman in the world
to forge these iron hooks with silver claws for you
They say wearing these will make you no different from ordinary people
and even allow you to harm others without detection
Perhaps this misfortune will prove to be a blessing in disguise
Do you take me for a child?
So easily fooled?
Every time something happens, you beat around the bush
trying to distract me
This time you even dared to lie to me
Could it be
that you're in league with that assassin?
Chen, that's so unfair!
I've served you with all my heart and soul
with utmost dedication
How could you think of me like that
Don't forget
who your real master is
Your Highness, please calm your anger
Chiyu will investigate the truth immediately
Get out
Yes
I understand now
I won't let you get hurt again
Zhu Huaijin
Why did you blow out the candle
Does he also know about the fire caused by this candlestick in the previous life
being knocked over
Could it be that he has also been reborn